bdoutdoors.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy - Online Privacy Policy - BDoutdoors Bloodydecks

### Privacy Policy – Short Version

BDoutdoors.com, Bloodydecks.com and all of the associated BD sites, as well as its owners and employees **HATE** Spam, Spammers, Junkmail and Phishing scams as much as we hate slow fishing and rough seas. We love our members and we will never sell or share your information with a third party.

The only way BDoutdoors.com will contact you is by Email via our newsletter, special event information or a special offer from one of our partners. If you don’t want ANY emails from BDoutdoors.com or other BD sites, you can click a link at the bottom of the Email and opt out permanently.

### Long Version (For the Lawyers)

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on a BD site or respond to a survey. When registering on BDoutdoors.com, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address and/or birth date. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to BD users based on the sites they visit and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google’s ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries and/or other requests or questions.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**  
How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction is complete, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?  
**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
**  
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

**Third-Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using any BD site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us  
**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [adminsupport@bdoutdoors.com](mailto:adminsupport@bdoutdoors.com) or by visiting[www.BDoutdoors.com](http://www.bdoutdoors.com/).

Edited 10/21/2011
